<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Persons on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Persons on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Button</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/andrew-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/andrew-button/</guid>
      <description>After a 15 year career with various businesses and economic development organizations, Andrew felt it was about time to move from being a ‘cheerleader’ and ‘curator’ of entrepreneurship to doing something that actually produced more entrepreneurs in rural communities.
​In 2014 he founded Mashup Lab; a for-more-than-profit company that activates rural ideas. That same year he launched a chapter of the Awesome Foundation in his community. Andrew has since gone on to launch another social enterprise - CO3, a fresh new coworking space for Freelancers, Entrepreneurs, and Independents located in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aristides Milios</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/aristides-milios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/aristides-milios/</guid>
      <description>Aristides is a highly motivated university student passionate about entrepreneurship, innovation, and web development.
CTO MicroCent Technologies and Co-Founder of Hoist Halifax, Aristides is full stack web developer who loves public speaking and is a natural leader. Smokin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Vardy</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/catherine-vardy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/catherine-vardy/</guid>
      <description>Catherine Vardy joined the Canadian Intellectual Property Office(CIPO) in 2015. As a Business Development Officer for the Atlantic Region, Catherine enjoys working with people to identify and highlight the value of IP.
As the Network Liaison and Program Manager at Springboard Atlantic, Catherine worked closely with innovative SMEs, universities and colleges. Catherine also worked in Atlantic Canada as a Research and Innovation Development Officer with the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Greene</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/charlie-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/charlie-greene/</guid>
      <description>Charlie is a senior software developer at The REDspace. He is alumni from Colibri Softwarewhere he worked for two years, ever since graduating from Acadia University with a Honors degree in Computer Science with Co-Op option.
Charlie&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by the work of Ruby the painting elephant. True story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Jordan</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/chris-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/chris-jordan/</guid>
      <description>Chris is a software developer with 16+ years experience with Henry Schein. Not to be pigeonholed, he&amp;rsquo;s got his hand in all sorts of things: Top tier support for an installation base spanning 2000+ customers, Brand development, Application planning and development, Database design, Documentation, Testing, Training, Training material development: web, print and video, Customer support, Installer creation, Phone system programming.
Chris&amp;rsquo; profile pic is a mashup of a picture of his swiped from Facebook and R2D2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Daniel Silver</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/dr-daniel-silver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/dr-daniel-silver/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Daniel L. Silver is the Director of the Acadia Institute for Data Analytics. He is also a Professor in and currently the Acting-Director of the Jodrey School of Computer Scienceat Acadia University. His areas of research and application are machine learning, data mining, and data analytics. His expertise is in Lifelong Machine Learning and Transfer Learning. He has published over 65 scientific papers and has co-chaired or been part of program committees for a number of national and international conferences, seminars and workshops on data mining and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Garrett</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/elizabeth-garrett/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/elizabeth-garrett/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just like becoming an expert in wine - you learn by drinking it, the best you can afford - you learn great food by finding the best there is, whether simply or luxurious. Then you savor it, analyze it, discuss it with your companions, and you compare it with other experiences&amp;rdquo; - Julia Child, Mastering the Art of French Cooking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emily Konrath</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/emily-konrath/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/emily-konrath/</guid>
      <description>Emily is a small business enthusiast with a passion for homegrown talent. Emily was born and raised in Wolfville, studied her Bachelor of Commerce degree at Saint Mary’s University and obtained her Masters in International Business from Jönköping, Sweden. Emily has lived and studied in cities across Canada and abroad in Germany and Sweden.
Emily is an Economic Development Officer with the Valley Regional Enterprise Network, a municipal corporation that works as a catalyst for regional economic development in the Annapolis Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frances Schagen</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/frances-schagen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/frances-schagen/</guid>
      <description>Frances is a small business innovator. She geeks out over business strategy, business models and building entrepreneurial ecosystems. She believe that&amp;rsquo;s the kind of thinking we need to save the world. Frances helps create places where entrepreneurship can thrive within our business and within our community.
Business innovation is essential for us to solve our biggest issues and to succeed in the world today. Business theory was developed for large business and small business is not a little big business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoff Crouse</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/geoff-crouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/geoff-crouse/</guid>
      <description>Geoff has more than 17 years of combined Software Engineering and Information Technology Consulting experience.
 Technical Sales Engineer, specializing in medium to large scale Drupal CMS projects including new development, site audits and analysis, and expert support services.
 Account Management, coordinating customer projects with engineering and support teams from initial conception to final delivery, and continued support.
  Geoff&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by a robot inspired by Peggy&amp;rsquo;s Cove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian McKay</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/ian-mckay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/ian-mckay/</guid>
      <description>“Creative Technician”&amp;hellip;what the heck is that?
I see my role, primarily, as that of a possibilitist. I listen closely to your ideas, what you hope to create, the problem you are working and then share with you the possibilities technology may offer. My years of immersion in Maker culture, joyfully exploring new and unusual uses for the wonders of emerging and age-old tech, provide me with a deep pool of possible solutions to your creative problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Frost</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/john-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/john-frost/</guid>
      <description>John Frost is a Senior Manager, Satellite Products, at PrecisionHawk. John worked extensively in geophysical research and exploration before returning to university to complete studies in International Relations/Intercultural Studies. With broad national and international project exposure, he is a cross-cultural specialist in technology adaptation. Through the Aerhyve brand, the company focused on the analysis of UAV data with Machine Learning, providing actionable intelligence for agricultural and industrial applications. An entrepreneur and technophile, John is always pursuing opportunities which make a local-global impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bezanson</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/justin-bezanson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/justin-bezanson/</guid>
      <description>Since 2000 I have continued to expand my knowledge and skills and worked hard to be the best developer I can be.
I enjoy meeting challenges and working hard to find creative and user friendly solutions.
My goal is to continually improve my development process, delivering higher quality and efficiency.
Specialties: PHP, ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, CodeIgniter, Zend Framework, AJAX, Windows, Linux, MySQL, SQL Server, WordPress, ASP.NET
Justin, pictured here, is The Thing from the Fantastic Four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Diehl</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/keith-diehl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/keith-diehl/</guid>
      <description>Keith got his first glimpse of HTML with NCSA&amp;rsquo;s Mosaic browser in 1994. A few “View Sources” later and he was hooked.
Soon after, he got his first web job as Webmaster for the Arizona Daily Wildcat. Over the years, Keith has worked for several newspapers and Fortune 500 companies including Coca Cola and Aflac insurance. He has been the Webmaster for North America&amp;rsquo;s premiere training provider CED Solutions for over 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Churchill Duke</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/laura-churchill-duke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/laura-churchill-duke/</guid>
      <description>Laura is a freelance Communications Specialist and Writer. She is a stay-at-home mom who does not stay at home! She works various contracts while working from home. Her primary job is running the website Valley Family Funwhich is a resource for families living in the Valley.
She is very involved with her community and participates in many volunteer activities.
Laura&amp;rsquo;s profile picture was created by software inspired by her painting inspired by Monet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Davis</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/mark-davis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/mark-davis/</guid>
      <description>Founder / CEO at colovo and co-founder of The HUB Yarmouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Hall</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/matt-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/matt-hall/</guid>
      <description>I make stuff happen at Agile*, an independent geoscience idea factory in Canada.
We build awesome knowledge engines for organizations (mostly wikis), and we hone our skills in subsurface science&amp;hellip; We have most recently been working on geothermal reservoir description. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked the Montney tight gas of Alberta and BC, frontier exploration in the Canadian Beaufort Sea, the Athabasca oil sands, the Norwegian North Sea. I also worked in software for several years, as an advocate of integrated volume visualization and interpretation and viz room pilot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Doucette</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/matthew-doucette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/matthew-doucette/</guid>
      <description>I am a video game developer (Xbox 360 &amp;amp; PC). Check out my video game company, Xona Games, and my first professional video game, Duality ZF, for more information. My only parter is my twin brother, Jason Doucette.
Here is the Duality ZF April 2009 trailer:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Caplan</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/max-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/max-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, he was born. What happened after this is the interesting part. Relatively speaking. After his long and tedious early childhood, Max found himself being introduced to the fascinating world of technology. One of his earliest experiences was with the beginner programming environment known as Scratch. After a couple of years of making awesome scratch projects, Max moved on to explore more that tech had to offer. Through his School he found himself on a Lego Robotics team for a couple years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Caplan</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/michael-caplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/michael-caplan/</guid>
      <description>Mike has been active as a web application developer and web designer for 16 years, working in the non-profit, university, retail, agricultural, and dental industries. He is a founding partner of HarvestHand, a platform that services Community Shared Agriculture farms. Mike founded Refresh Annapolis Valley, a new media professional association to help grow the Valley&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.
Mike is the Software Development Manager for the Labnet Dental Lab Systemsdivision of Henry Schein - a Fortune 300 company with a small footprint here in Wolfville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Richards</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/paul-richards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/paul-richards/</guid>
      <description>Paul Richards is innovacorp&amp;#39;sregional manager for Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s Annapolis Valley and South Shore. In this role, Paul focuses on enabling knowledge-based companies to accelerate their growth and helping foster a dynamic high-growth entrepreneurial culture in the region.
Paul spent over 10 years working with the Acadia Centre for Social and Business Entrepreneurship (ACSBE) assisting businesses in rural Nova Scotia. In this role, Paul also worked to build the entrepreneurial capacity and infrastructure of several developing economies in Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philip Kerr</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/philip-kerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/philip-kerr/</guid>
      <description>Philip is a Canadian lawyer, and Canadian patent and trademark agent with 29 years of experience. He is a partner in the Canadian patent firm of Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau(offices in Halifax and Ottawa).
Philip is also the president of PCTxs Inc., a firm that provides an online marketplace for selling/licensing patent application rights, particularly unexpired PCT national phase rights and unexpired Paris Convention patent application rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pierre Clouthier</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/pierre-clouthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/pierre-clouthier/</guid>
      <description>Co-founder, President, Progeny Genealogy Inc., specialising in computer graphics software for genealogy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Avery</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/trevor-avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/trevor-avery/</guid>
      <description>Trevor Avery is a marine biologist (Ph.D.) and biostatistician (P.Stat.) with a variety of research interests. U. of Guelph was home for his undergraduate Honours, Acadia U. for an M.Sc. (under Mike Dadswell) and Memorial U. for his Ph.D. (with Joe Brown, r.i.p.); Currently he is back with Acadia as an Associate Professor cross appointed within the faculties of Biology and Mathematics &amp;amp; Statistics.
Technology and analysis techniques (statistics) play a significant role in most of his research projects, but not all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/ulrike-bahr-gedalia/</guid>
      <description>Ulrike Bahr-Gedalia (BA, MA) is the President &amp;amp; CEO of Digital Nova Scotia. She’s a multilingual senior level executive with over 20 years of combined experience in the private, public &amp;amp; academic sectors. Her career spans five geographic regions: America (North), Africa (South), Middle East, Asia &amp;amp; Europe.
Ulrike thrives on challenges! With a proven track record in International Marketing, Business &amp;amp; Economic Development, Channel Management, Government/Stakeholder Relations, Board Governance, Fundraising, Organizational Growth &amp;amp; Public Speaking, she&amp;rsquo;s a true game-changer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wes Booth</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/wes-booth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/person/wes-booth/</guid>
      <description>Wes Booth literally grew up during the birth of social media. In 2006, he signed on Facebook for the first time and in 2013 he sent his first Snap. Wes started his first business when he was 14 and is now working on a project to better connect and support brands and creative talent in Nova Scotia through his social media community called We Are NS. Wes believes in Atlantic Canada 100% and is determined social media is a good place to start telling our stories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>