<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Organizations on Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
    <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organizations on Refresh Annapolis Valley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Computer Science Society</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-computer-science-society/</guid>
      <description>Need some info&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Entrepreneurship Centre</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-entrepreneurship-centre/</guid>
      <description>AEC has been developing and delivering workshops for business professionals, entrepreneurs, and not-for-profits for over 25 years. AEC continues to innovate and develop new and relevant programs for today’s business professional.
Rural Innovation Centre The Rural Innovation Centre (RIC) supports entrepreneurs and businesses in the Annapolis Valley and on the South Shore by providing training, advisory and consulting services to small businesses, government and not-for-profit organizations. The Rural Innovation Centre is an incubator for start up companies to access working space and support, networking events, mentors and connect to Acadia faculty and facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Institute for Data Analytics</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-institute-for-data-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Rural Canada feeds our nation literally, economically, and environmentally. It provides the food, fiber, minerals, water and other bio-resources and natural resources on which our country depends and the arteries of transportation by which they are delivered. Digital technologies and data analytics can help us shape how we work with these resources and their impact on our local communities and our planet.
Mission To advance knowledge in data analytics through collaborative and interdisciplinary research, education and outreach and to foster the ethical application and commercialization of data analytic solutions to challenges facing industry, government and society in rural Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acadia Robotics Program</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/acadia-robotics-program/</guid>
      <description>The Robot Programming Competition mission is to increase interest in building digital technology and computer science by engaging Nova Scotia students in annual robotics programming competitions and related activities that feature problem solving and teamwork.
The Acadia Robotics Program, through the Jodrey School of Computer Science, depends heavily on financial support from external organizations and the committed volunteers who annually contribute to the season from late August through to mid-June. We have a junior program, FIRST® LEGO® League, and a senior program, Robofest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annapolis Valley STEAMspace</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/annapolis-valley-steamspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/annapolis-valley-steamspace/</guid>
      <description>A place for Annapolis Valley Makers, inventors, artists, entrepreneurs, tinkerers and the like to meet, share ideas and work towards establishing the proposed Acadia University STEAMspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CO3</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/co3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/co3/</guid>
      <description>CO3 is a fresh bew co-working space for freelancers, entrepreneurs and independents.
CO3 Is a concept created by ​Andrew Button, a social entrepreneur based in Bridgewater, Nova Scotia.
&amp;ldquo;The mission is to create a space that further cultivates rural Nova Scotia&amp;rsquo;s freelance economy.&amp;rdquo;
Through the success of his own company Mashup Lab and other social ventures ​he&amp;rsquo;s discovered a lot of hidden talent in the Maritimes which he feels needs more room to grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Intellectual Property Office </title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/canadian-intellectual-property-office/</guid>
      <description>The Canadian Intellectual Property Office (CIPO), a Special Operating Agency (SOA) associated with Innovation, Science and Economic Development Canada, is responsible for the administration and processing of the greater part of intellectual property in Canada. CIPO&amp;rsquo;s areas of activity include:
 Patents cover new inventions (process, machine, manufacture, composition of matter), or any new and useful improvement of an existing invention;
 A trademark is a word (or words), a design, or a combination of these, used to identify the goods or services of one person or organization and to distinguish these goods or services from those of others in the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colibri Software</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/colibri-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/colibri-software/</guid>
      <description>Colibri Software builds awesome software. We work with our clients to understand their needs and then produce a simple and effective solution to their problems. Our focus is on making a product easy to use, from websites to mobile apps, we like it when we hear “this is easy”.
We have a special affinity for mapping projects and have send rugged phone apps as far as Nunavut to help collect data for the hunting community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nova Scotia</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/digital-nova-scotia/</guid>
      <description>Engaging both members and stakeholders in the region, Digital Nova Scotia provides advocacy, multi-sectoral industry intelligence, facilitates connections between industry and talent, and delivers high-level programming to ensure Nova Scotia’s $1.5 billion digital industry (which boasts an additional $1 billion in spin-offs) continues to flourish.
IT starts here. IT stays here. IT grows here. As the industry association for the fastest growing sector in the province with the highest number of ICT graduates per capita in Canada, Digital Nova Scotia encourages our tech talent and growing ecosystem of digital businesses to start here, stay here, and grow here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUB Kentville</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/hub-kentville/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/hub-kentville/</guid>
      <description>Get Inspired, Get Connected, Get involved. HUB spaces provide an inspirational home to members and are a focal point for change within the local communities.
What is the Hub? The HUB is about the power of innovation through collaboration.
We believe there is no shortage of good ideas to solve the issues of our time. But there is an acute lack of collaboration and support structures to help make them happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HarvestHand</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/harvesthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/harvesthand/</guid>
      <description>HarvestHand is a community platform dedicated to strengthening regional food systems. We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about supporting farms with CSA&amp;rsquo;s to become more profitable using HarvestHand CSA Software, helping communities eat better through the HarvestHand Community, creating good jobs in rural communities, and building new media solutions that make sharing the harvest easier.
Our vision is to create new media solutions that strengthen regional food systems&amp;rsquo; ability to succeed in value oriented approaches to production, distribution, consumption and community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jodrey School of Computer Science</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/jodrey-school-of-computer-science-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>The Jodrey School of Computer Science prepares students for today&amp;rsquo;s ever changing world of technology in a unique, fully mobile computing environment. Students develop a thorough understanding of computer systems software, modern software design methods and computer systems software.
Students in all degree programs complete a self-directed project during the course of their studies. This provides students with the opportunity to work closely with professors and to apply knowledge acquired through experiment and real-life application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerr &amp; Nadeau</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/kerr--nadeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/kerr--nadeau/</guid>
      <description>At Kerr &amp;amp; Nadeau our job is to de-mystify and to simplify the rules for you, to offer you sound professional advice and superior legal services that will enable you, whether you are an inventor, an entrepreneur or a corporate executive, to execute your business plan, to protect your legal rights and to realize your strategic objectives while mitigating risk and ensuring compliance. Risk is the bane and Achilles heel of most business enterprises, and the single greatest obstacle to achieving your mission critical goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labnet Dental Lab Systems</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/labnet-dental-lab-systems/</guid>
      <description>Labnet Dental Lab Systems offers the Dental Lab industry&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive and powerful management systems with solutions suited for labs of all sizes and budgets. Whether your lab is a thriving multi-site corporation or a one-technician miracle lab, we have a perfect fit for you.
As a Henry Schein company, you can depend on Labnet Dental Lab Systems for stability and providing your dentists with the latest technological advancements. When you are operating within tight deadlines, the last thing you should worry about is your software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launchbox</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/launchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/launchbox/</guid>
      <description>Launchbox is the centre for student entrepreneurs, located on the 4th floor of Patterson Hall at Acadia University. We support students in their entrepreneurial pursuits by providing free programming, networking, access to mentors, and other entrepreneurs, working space and competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PrecisionHawk</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/precisionhawk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/precisionhawk/</guid>
      <description>PrecisionHawk is the leading provider of aerial data and safety platforms for drones. The Lancaster is PrecisionHawk’s fixed-wing, autonomous drone built to collect the highest quality terrestrial data using a host of integrated sensors including visual, thermal, LiDAR, multispectral and hyperspectral. PrecisionHawk houses three divisions that support its mission: DataMapper aerial mapping and analysis software, TerraServer satellite imagery and LATAS (Low Altitude Traffic and Airspace Safety).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progeny Genealogy</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/progeny-genealogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/progeny-genealogy/</guid>
      <description>Progeny Genealogy is the leading developer of family tree software and other useful, easy-to-use genealogy research resources, including Charting Companion™, Genelines™ and Map My Family Tree™. More than pretty charts, our genealogy software programs are also powerful research tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R-bar</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/r-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/r-bar/</guid>
      <description>R-bar is Acadia University&amp;rsquo;s scientific programming study group. They cover everything R: a programming language and software environment for statistical computing and graphics.
WHAT WE DO  Skill Sharing: Share your favorite coding skills and tools with your friends and colleagues in friendly, no-pressure work-alongs.
 Co-Working: Get together to work on your coding projects, help each other out and share your work.
 Community Building: Meet new people in your field, organization or community - and find out what we can do when we work together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Annapolis Valley</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/refresh-annapolis-valley/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;terminal-error&#34;&gt;Terminal Error&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recursive meta loop&lt;/strong&gt;.  Stack overflow.  Core now being dumped&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScotiaCom</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/scotiacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/scotiacom/</guid>
      <description>ScotiaCom (aka Scotia Computer Resources Inc.) is a small, independent business located in the Annapolis Valley, Nova Scotia. What started as an educational software development company has become a leader in the development and deployment of services that allow organizations, groups, individuals and small businesses to take full advantage of the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The HUB South Shore</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/the-hub-south-shore/</guid>
      <description>The HUB South Shore is a coworking space that connects progressive businesses and people together so innovation and enterprise can thrive. We enjoy the freedom to run our own lives and depend on the motivation, productivity, and creativity that comes from working with others.
Our vision is for a self-reliant rural economy rooted in the collaboration of local entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The HUB Yarmouth</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/the-hub-yarmouth/</guid>
      <description>Creative shared space The Hub is a co-working space for creative and social entrepreneurs in Yarmouth, Nova Scotia, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valley Family Fun</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/valley-family-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/valley-family-fun/</guid>
      <description>People who are new to the area (and some who are not) often ask Laura Churchill Dukewhat they can do with their families in the Valley.
This made her realize that there isn’t one central place to look for information. Valley Family Fun is a compilation of what she&amp;rsquo;s discovered! Follow VFF on their Facebook group too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are NS</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/we-are-ns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/we-are-ns/</guid>
      <description>Nova Scotia’s portfolio of the very best people, products, and places. We Are NS&amp;rsquo; mission is to celebrate the very best brands and creative talent Nova Scotia has to offer one story at a time. Our vision is to create a vibrant community of people who build confidence among Nova Scotians by challenging themselves and supporting others to be better every day.
Join us and use the hashtag #WeAreNS to help us share our story to the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women in Science and Engineering at Acadia</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/women-in-science-and-engineering-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>WISE (Women in Science and Engineering) at Acadia is a group of female faculty members from the Faculty of Pure and Applied Science and Kinesiology who gather together to address the unique issues that women in academia face. The group has supported learning opportunities and award applications for Acadia women faculty members. After a gathering held in October 2014 additional WISE priorities have been identified related to mentoring, science camps for young women, and a course offering for undergraduates in Women and Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women&#39;s and Gender Studies</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/women-and-gender-studies-at-acadia-university/</guid>
      <description>In 1973, Acadia University became one of the first universities in Canada to offer a course in Women&amp;rsquo;s Studies. The course, entitled Women in the Modern World, was the cornerstone of a program which in three decades has developed a multi-disciplinary approach to teaching and research in gender-related issues. Faculty members from the Arts, Pure and Applied Sciences, Education, Kinesiology, and Theatre contribute to the program on a rotational basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>innovacorp</title>
      <link>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/innovacorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://refreshannapolisvalley.com/organization/innovacorp/</guid>
      <description>Innovacorp is Nova Scotia’s early stage venture capital organization. We work to find, fund and foster innovative Nova Scotia start-ups that strive to change the world. Early stage investment is at the core of our business model. We also give entrepreneurs access to world-class incubation facilities, expert advice and other support to help them accelerate their companies.
Target industries include clean technology, information technology, life sciences and ocean technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>